<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hardware on Some Random Website</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/tags/hardware/</link><description>Recent content in Hardware on Some Random Website</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ta180m.github.io/tags/hardware/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Worst First Build - Homelab Operational!</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/worst-first-build-6/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/worst-first-build-6/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
Over the past week, I&amp;rsquo;ve been getting my new build set up. It&amp;rsquo;s been quite satisfying: I&amp;rsquo;ll run into more than my fair share of issues, but problem solving for the win!
The OS installation went relatively smoothly. Partitioning disks was a bit tricky but I got it to work. I wanted to try out systemd-networkd and systemd-boot for my new server, and I had to spend some time researching documentation.</description></item><item><title>Worst First Build - Live on PCPartPicker!</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/worst-first-build-5/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/worst-first-build-5/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
It&amp;rsquo;s time to go full circle! I first started planning my build using Logical Increments and PCPartPicker and I can&amp;rsquo;t appreciate how much they&amp;rsquo;ve helped me the confusing world of PC building. Now that my build is &amp;ldquo;finished&amp;rdquo;, or more accurately, functional, it&amp;rsquo;s time to publish it on PCPartPicker!
Here&amp;rsquo;s some anticlimactic images of the completed build:
Here&amp;rsquo;s the writeup that I did for the build:</description></item><item><title>Worst First Build - How to Get a Free GPU During the World's Worst GPU Shortage Ever</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/worst-first-build-4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/worst-first-build-4/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
The Great GPU Shortage continues to smash records. We live in ludicrous times indeed, where it&amp;rsquo;s considered lucky to win a lottery to buy a $330 GPU&amp;hellip; at a $200 markup! The barometer of Bitcoin and Ethereum prices continues to skyrocket, and my chances of finally getting a GPU and finishing my build were dimming every day with no end in sight.
But finish my build I did, with a GPU that ended up costing a grand total of&amp;hellip; $0.</description></item><item><title>Worst First Build - The Quest for a GPU</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/worst-first-build-3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/worst-first-build-3/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
Last Wednesday, March 10th, was going to be the day. The day I finally could complete a functioning (but incomplete) build. My slightly overpriced RAM sticks (RAM prices were creeping upward sinisterly so I decided I probably shouldn&amp;rsquo;t wait longer. Probably a bad move, too, but whatever.) were arriving, and it was going to be momentous. I was going to boot up an Arch USB drive, SSH in, and get the party going.</description></item><item><title>Worst First Build - The Sad Saga Continues</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/worst-first-build-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/worst-first-build-2/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
What a perfect time to build a PC: massive supply chain disruptions, cryptocurrencies driving up GPU prices through the roof, (scalper) bot wars, and a pesky little thing called the coronavirus murdering 2.5 million people (that last one probably sounds completely alien to anyone before 2019). Just perfect!
Anyways&amp;hellip; for over 40 days since buying an overpriced 5600X (because of insane taxes, that&amp;rsquo;s what), there were a grand total of zero deals.</description></item><item><title>Worst First Build</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/worst-first-build/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/worst-first-build/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
My laptop&amp;rsquo;s starting to get old. I mean, it works perfectly fine for the most part, but open up a few Google Docs at the same time and watch it struggle to load them: its age is starting to show. Or try to run Zoom (sandboxed in a browser, of course) and anything else at the simultaneously, and you&amp;rsquo;ll get an ugly surprise when your Zoom audio starts crackling up really bad and the other app lags like crazy.</description></item></channel></rss>