<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Windows on Some Random Website</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/tags/windows/</link><description>Recent content in Windows on Some Random Website</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ta180m.github.io/tags/windows/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>An Interview with GitHub Copilot</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/interview-github-copilot/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/interview-github-copilot/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
The hype is real!
Not only can Copilot write code, it can also talk with you in a text file. Unfortunately, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to work with the open source build of Visual Studio Code, so I hopped into my Ubuntu VM and installed the proprietary VSCode build. Anyways, Copilot said some pretty&amp;hellip; questionable things&amp;hellip;
ME: Hello GitHub Copilot!
AI: Hello!
ME: How are you?</description></item><item><title>Does Windows Really Suck?</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/does-windows-really-suck/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/does-windows-really-suck/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
Well, obviously yes.
But recently, I heard about official support for GUI apps in WSL, so I thought I&amp;rsquo;d give it a try. Plus, my computer is on the Windows Insider dev channel, so I have to boot up and update Windows every few months anyways.
So I booted up Windows for the first time in a few months, and it was&amp;hellip; slow. That&amp;rsquo;s all that I can describe it as.</description></item><item><title>How Windows Update Saved My Computer from... Windows Update</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/windows-update/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/windows-update/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
If I had to name the single thing that I most hate about Windows, it would probably be Windows update. I have a long and complicated history with Windows update. Throw in Windows Insider, and you have the perfect recipe for disaster!
A close encounter So my experience with Windows update begins about two or three years ago, when I noticed the cute ninja cat of Windows Insider lounging at the bottom of the Updates panel in the Windows 10 settings app.</description></item><item><title>The Linux Office?</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/linux-office/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/linux-office/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
OK, LibreOffice may not be the most loved application out there, but it&amp;rsquo;s enough for most people. I use LibreOffice even on Windows! However, there is one thing about it that bothers me: the hideous icons! At first, I thought it might be caused be anti-aliasing or my screen scaling (currently set at 1.5x so everything&amp;rsquo;s not tiny) but nope! The icons stayed hideous no matter what I did.</description></item><item><title>iOS Jailbreaking || Why the World is Just a Programming Task</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/ios-jailbreaking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/ios-jailbreaking/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
Let&amp;rsquo;s do this &amp;ldquo;episode&amp;rdquo; style:
Episode 0 (Because no true programmer would start a list with 1) In fourth or fifth grade, a friend told me about all the cool things he was doing with his jailbroken iPhone.
This is EXACTLY like your friend telling you about how fun and awesome competitive programming is.
I wasn&amp;rsquo;t impressed.
Episode 1 Five years later&amp;hellip;
After doing some TI-Nspire, Wii U, and Switch hacking, I set my eyes on my lowly iPhone 6s with a cracked screen that I&amp;rsquo;m procrastinating to fix.</description></item></channel></rss>