<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>fun on Some Random Website</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/tags/fun/</link><description>Recent content in fun on Some Random Website</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 21:52:58 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ta180m.github.io/tags/fun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Installing Every Arch Package</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/installing-every-arch-package/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 21:52:58 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/installing-every-arch-package/</guid><description>Challenge accepted. Let&amp;rsquo;s do it!
First things first, let&amp;rsquo;s generate a list of all official Arch Linux packages. Fortunately, pacman, the best pragmatic package manager in existence, makes this a breeze.
pacman -Sql Great, now let&amp;rsquo;s install it all!
pacman -Sql | xargs sudo pacman -S 10 seconds later, you&amp;rsquo;ll find yourself with&amp;hellip; unresolvable package conflicts detected?
OK, fine, let&amp;rsquo;s disable dependency checking then:
pacman -Sql | xargs sudo pacman -Sdd Nope, didn&amp;rsquo;t work.</description></item><item><title>Fun Stuff From My Old Website</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/fun-stuff-from-my-old-website/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 21:38:53 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/fun-stuff-from-my-old-website/</guid><description>I discovered this gem in my old website&amp;rsquo;s source code and it&amp;rsquo;s awesome. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure why it never got published, since it obviously deserves it!
A semi-serious humorous list of things I hate Bananas (foods containing bananas are fine though) CRLF UTF-16 The name of the letter W Loading screens US customary units The metric system (not as much as customary units) Non-absolute temperature scales (Kelvins are the real deal) Time zones AM and PM systemd haters systemd Burritos DOCX Zoom&amp;rsquo;s Linux client (worst Linux app ever) The Electron framework The fact that the USACO website doesn&amp;rsquo;t use HTTPS OpenLDAP Manjaro haters Manjaro iOS jailbreaking People with lists of things they hate Nvidia drivers Blender propoganda on exotube Western Sahara messing up world maps All the people with exozyme accounts but haven&amp;rsquo;t ever logged in Drawing blood Weebs Being accused of being a weeb Cryptocurrencies The Discord TOS Phones with more than two cameras X11 Ubuntu haters Ubuntu People with lists of things they hate with both a certain thing and haters of that thing on the same list Standalone window managers The length of copyright in the US The MIT License The GitHub Desktop app GitHub Swimming</description></item></channel></rss>