<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Rant on Some Random Website</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/tags/rant/</link><description>Recent content in Rant on Some Random Website</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 21:38:53 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ta180m.github.io/tags/rant/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fun Stuff From My Old Website</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/fun-stuff-from-my-old-website/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 21:38:53 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/fun-stuff-from-my-old-website/</guid><description>I discovered this gem in my old website&amp;rsquo;s source code and it&amp;rsquo;s awesome. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure why it never got published, since it obviously deserves it!
A semi-serious humorous list of things I hate Bananas (foods containing bananas are fine though) CRLF UTF-16 The name of the letter W Loading screens US customary units The metric system (not as much as customary units) Non-absolute temperature scales (Kelvins are the real deal) Time zones AM and PM systemd haters systemd Burritos DOCX Zoom&amp;rsquo;s Linux client (worst Linux app ever) The Electron framework The fact that the USACO website doesn&amp;rsquo;t use HTTPS OpenLDAP Manjaro haters Manjaro iOS jailbreaking People with lists of things they hate Nvidia drivers Blender propoganda on exotube Western Sahara messing up world maps All the people with exozyme accounts but haven&amp;rsquo;t ever logged in Drawing blood Weebs Being accused of being a weeb Cryptocurrencies The Discord TOS Phones with more than two cameras X11 Ubuntu haters Ubuntu People with lists of things they hate with both a certain thing and haters of that thing on the same list Standalone window managers The length of copyright in the US The MIT License The GitHub Desktop app GitHub Swimming</description></item><item><title>The Anti Window Manager</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/anti-window-manager/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/anti-window-manager/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
KDE bloat, WMs rule. Therefore, we must use get rid of the DE in KDE and we are left with&amp;hellip; everyone&amp;rsquo;s favorite WM, KWin!
There are only three easy steps. First, set up the environmental variables and start up D-Bus:
export $(dbus-launch) export QT_QPA_PLATFORM=wayland Now enjoy your super unbloated standalone compositing Wayland window manager with kwin_wayland konsole. Need XWayland? To add that extra bloat, just pass the --xwayland flag.</description></item><item><title>Plasma 5.22 is a Disappointment</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/plasma-5.22-disappointment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/plasma-5.22-disappointment/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
The KDE Plasma update train has cycled back again to another major update, so I snatched Plasma 5.22 from the very scary testing repository, took it for a spin, and it&amp;rsquo;s&amp;hellip; disappointing.
What&amp;rsquo;s the big new feature this time? Adaptive transparency, apparently.
Adaptive what?
Yeah, if you were expecting something big, another huge leap forward, this update was anything but that. If you think panel transparency is a big deal, think again.</description></item><item><title>The Myth of Bloat</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/myth-bloat/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/myth-bloat/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
If there&amp;rsquo;s one thing that hardcore Linux users are ridiculously obsessed about, it&amp;rsquo;s the vague and scary concept of bloat. You gotta keep package counts low, use WMs, and compile suckless.org stuff. Visit any Arch or Gentoo forum or chat, and this philosophy seems to be epidemical. But&amp;hellip; there&amp;rsquo;s a gaping problem: package count is totally irrelevant, WMs are painful to configure, and suckless.org software really sucks.</description></item><item><title>Self-hosting Sucks</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/self-hosting-sucks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/self-hosting-sucks/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
After one month of self-hosting, if there&amp;rsquo;s one thing I&amp;rsquo;ve learned, it&amp;rsquo;s that self-hosting sucks. As I&amp;rsquo;ve said in a previous post, self-hosting is not the solution to our privacy woes. So why exactly does it suck so much? Here&amp;rsquo;s a short timeline of the past month:
My Discord-Matrix bridge goes down over a weekend and I don&amp;rsquo;t find out for several days.</description></item><item><title>The Web Sucks!</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/web-sucks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/web-sucks/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
suckless.org really hates the web. I&amp;rsquo;ll quote them directly:
It has enabled the global information exchange, mass surveillance, studies in social control, allowed revolutions, made a fortune for many billionaires and in the meanwhile ruined our climate: the web.
There is an industry which is specialized on extending the resource usage to display just some characters on your display. Millions of jobs are based on outputting HTML in an inefficient way.</description></item><item><title>Why WMs Suck</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/why-wms-suck/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/why-wms-suck/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
WM fans, don&amp;rsquo;t kill me for saying this, but window managers suck. To see why, let&amp;rsquo;s examine the process of installing and configuring a WM.
Installing a WM OK, I&amp;rsquo;ll admit that this step is much faster. Most WMs are only a few megabytes and take a few seconds to install, even with slow package managers like urpmi. Try installing something like KDE Plasma on Mageia or even Arch.</description></item></channel></rss>