<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>KDE on Some Random Website</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/tags/kde/</link><description>Recent content in KDE on Some Random Website</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 20:51:58 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ta180m.github.io/tags/kde/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Make Wayland Scaling Less Painful</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/make-wayland-scaling-less-painful/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 20:51:58 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/make-wayland-scaling-less-painful/</guid><description>Wayland is awesome. It supports my 4K 60Hz monitor out-of-the-box without any Xorg configuration or custom EDID file hackery. Even gaming on Wayland more or less works.
There&amp;rsquo;s only one problem or I would have ditched Xorg forever.
Everything on the 4K monitor is really really tiny! You might say, why not just apply some scaling? After all, KDE Plasma has great fraction scaling support and just works™ on Xorg. The problem is that Wayland apps scale perfectly but XWayland apps&amp;hellip; not so much.</description></item><item><title>Plasma 5.22 is a Disappointment</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/plasma-5.22-disappointment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/plasma-5.22-disappointment/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
The KDE Plasma update train has cycled back again to another major update, so I snatched Plasma 5.22 from the very scary testing repository, took it for a spin, and it&amp;rsquo;s&amp;hellip; disappointing.
What&amp;rsquo;s the big new feature this time? Adaptive transparency, apparently.
Adaptive what?
Yeah, if you were expecting something big, another huge leap forward, this update was anything but that. If you think panel transparency is a big deal, think again.</description></item><item><title>Fixing Bugs Isn't Hard!</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/fixing-bugs-isnt-hard/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/fixing-bugs-isnt-hard/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
A few days ago, I wanted to record my screen, and in process, I discovered this bug. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem like a very complicated bug, right? Just look through the code, find out what&amp;rsquo;s wrong, and send in a pull request! Or is it that easy?
The first issue is that Spectacle&amp;rsquo;s code is not exactly the most readable code out there, but I was able to identify [line 209 in GUI/KSMainWindow.</description></item><item><title>How to Break a Rolling Release</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/break-rolling-release/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/break-rolling-release/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
It&amp;rsquo;s the day! Plasma 5.21 is out!
First, let me flex my neofetch to answer all your burning questions about my OS:
Now, time for the update. The big one. The closest thing to a point update in a rolling release. And&amp;hellip;
Lots of updates, but Plasma 5.21 is not one of them.
Digging a bit deeper, it looks like it&amp;rsquo;s still in testing. Looks like we need to enable it first.</description></item></channel></rss>