<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Some Random Website</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Some Random Website</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 21:52:58 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ta180m.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Installing Every Arch Package</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/installing-every-arch-package/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 21:52:58 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/installing-every-arch-package/</guid><description>Challenge accepted. Let&amp;rsquo;s do it!
First things first, let&amp;rsquo;s generate a list of all official Arch Linux packages. Fortunately, pacman, the best pragmatic package manager in existence, makes this a breeze.
pacman -Sql Great, now let&amp;rsquo;s install it all!
pacman -Sql | xargs sudo pacman -S 10 seconds later, you&amp;rsquo;ll find yourself with&amp;hellip; unresolvable package conflicts detected?
OK, fine, let&amp;rsquo;s disable dependency checking then:
pacman -Sql | xargs sudo pacman -Sdd Nope, didn&amp;rsquo;t work.</description></item><item><title>Fun Stuff From My Old Website</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/fun-stuff-from-my-old-website/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 21:38:53 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/fun-stuff-from-my-old-website/</guid><description>I discovered this gem in my old website&amp;rsquo;s source code and it&amp;rsquo;s awesome. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure why it never got published, since it obviously deserves it!
A semi-serious humorous list of things I hate Bananas (foods containing bananas are fine though) CRLF UTF-16 The name of the letter W Loading screens US customary units The metric system (not as much as customary units) Non-absolute temperature scales (Kelvins are the real deal) Time zones AM and PM systemd haters systemd Burritos DOCX Zoom&amp;rsquo;s Linux client (worst Linux app ever) The Electron framework The fact that the USACO website doesn&amp;rsquo;t use HTTPS OpenLDAP Manjaro haters Manjaro iOS jailbreaking People with lists of things they hate Nvidia drivers Blender propoganda on exotube Western Sahara messing up world maps All the people with exozyme accounts but haven&amp;rsquo;t ever logged in Drawing blood Weebs Being accused of being a weeb Cryptocurrencies The Discord TOS Phones with more than two cameras X11 Ubuntu haters Ubuntu People with lists of things they hate with both a certain thing and haters of that thing on the same list Standalone window managers The length of copyright in the US The MIT License The GitHub Desktop app GitHub Swimming</description></item><item><title>Gitea is the Future!</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/gitea-is-the-future/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 19:43:29 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/gitea-is-the-future/</guid><description>The single most important piece of FOSS news that I&amp;rsquo;ve seen in years just dropped earlier this week. Yes, this is more important than KDE&amp;rsquo;s 25th Anniversary release, Lenovo&amp;rsquo;s OEM Linux laptops, the Steam Deck, and the Pinephone. Gitea is joining the fediverse!
OK, not quite yet. They did get a ton of funding though, so let&amp;rsquo;s hope it&amp;rsquo;s implemented quickly. Maybe by the end of the year?
So why is this important?</description></item><item><title>Make Wayland Scaling Less Painful</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/make-wayland-scaling-less-painful/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 20:51:58 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/make-wayland-scaling-less-painful/</guid><description>Wayland is awesome. It supports my 4K 60Hz monitor out-of-the-box without any Xorg configuration or custom EDID file hackery. Even gaming on Wayland more or less works.
There&amp;rsquo;s only one problem or I would have ditched Xorg forever.
Everything on the 4K monitor is really really tiny! You might say, why not just apply some scaling? After all, KDE Plasma has great fraction scaling support and just works™ on Xorg. The problem is that Wayland apps scale perfectly but XWayland apps&amp;hellip; not so much.</description></item><item><title>Find Deleted Matrix Messages</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/find-deleted-matrix-messages/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 22:07:26 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/find-deleted-matrix-messages/</guid><description>It feels like I haven&amp;rsquo;t written a blog post in forever, and plus, I want to test Hugo&amp;rsquo;s code block formatting.
Anyways, time for something actually fun and useful&amp;hellip;
So you self-host a Matrix server, right? If not, this guide won&amp;rsquo;t be very useful. It&amp;rsquo;s still hilarious though.
If you ever get tired of ghost pings or trolls quickly deleting their Matrix messages, you can troll them right back. The Synapse Matrix server keeps deleted messages for about a week in the database before permanently deleting them.</description></item><item><title>Redesigning My Website</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/redesigning-my-website/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 19:25:13 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/redesigning-my-website/</guid><description>My old website sucked. Like, for real. It was a bit of hard-written HTML plus a Jekyll blog, and it was a huge pain to update and maintain. GitHub kept randomly emailing me about various security vulnerabilities in some Ruby dependency of Jekyll, and hard-written HTML can only get you so far before you rage-quit.
So what now? Well, I did write a different site using the Hugo static site generator, howtuwu, and it turned out really nice.</description></item><item><title>Hello, world!</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 22:14:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/hello-world/</guid><description>Welcome to my new website!</description></item><item><title>An Interview with GitHub Copilot</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/interview-github-copilot/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/interview-github-copilot/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
The hype is real!
Not only can Copilot write code, it can also talk with you in a text file. Unfortunately, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to work with the open source build of Visual Studio Code, so I hopped into my Ubuntu VM and installed the proprietary VSCode build. Anyways, Copilot said some pretty&amp;hellip; questionable things&amp;hellip;
ME: Hello GitHub Copilot!
AI: Hello!
ME: How are you?</description></item><item><title>The Anti Window Manager</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/anti-window-manager/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/anti-window-manager/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
KDE bloat, WMs rule. Therefore, we must use get rid of the DE in KDE and we are left with&amp;hellip; everyone&amp;rsquo;s favorite WM, KWin!
There are only three easy steps. First, set up the environmental variables and start up D-Bus:
export $(dbus-launch) export QT_QPA_PLATFORM=wayland Now enjoy your super unbloated standalone compositing Wayland window manager with kwin_wayland konsole. Need XWayland? To add that extra bloat, just pass the --xwayland flag.</description></item><item><title>Plasma 5.22 is a Disappointment</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/plasma-5.22-disappointment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/plasma-5.22-disappointment/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
The KDE Plasma update train has cycled back again to another major update, so I snatched Plasma 5.22 from the very scary testing repository, took it for a spin, and it&amp;rsquo;s&amp;hellip; disappointing.
What&amp;rsquo;s the big new feature this time? Adaptive transparency, apparently.
Adaptive what?
Yeah, if you were expecting something big, another huge leap forward, this update was anything but that. If you think panel transparency is a big deal, think again.</description></item><item><title>The Myth of Bloat</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/myth-bloat/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/myth-bloat/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
If there&amp;rsquo;s one thing that hardcore Linux users are ridiculously obsessed about, it&amp;rsquo;s the vague and scary concept of bloat. You gotta keep package counts low, use WMs, and compile suckless.org stuff. Visit any Arch or Gentoo forum or chat, and this philosophy seems to be epidemical. But&amp;hellip; there&amp;rsquo;s a gaping problem: package count is totally irrelevant, WMs are painful to configure, and suckless.org software really sucks.</description></item><item><title>Does Windows Really Suck?</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/does-windows-really-suck/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/does-windows-really-suck/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
Well, obviously yes.
But recently, I heard about official support for GUI apps in WSL, so I thought I&amp;rsquo;d give it a try. Plus, my computer is on the Windows Insider dev channel, so I have to boot up and update Windows every few months anyways.
So I booted up Windows for the first time in a few months, and it was&amp;hellip; slow. That&amp;rsquo;s all that I can describe it as.</description></item><item><title>Putting the Wacom Tablet to Good Use!</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/putting-wacom-tablet-good-use/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/putting-wacom-tablet-good-use/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
I&amp;rsquo;ve had a Wacom tablet for a long time now, but there&amp;rsquo;s just never been a legitimate use for it, really. Everything that I could do with the tablet, I could also do with my laptop&amp;rsquo;s touchscreen and stylus, so it always seemed like a bit of a waste. Sure, the drawing experience is a little bit better, the screen is a bit larger, but why use a Wacom tablet when the touchscreen and stylus work just fine?</description></item><item><title>Desktop Linux Revisited</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/desktop-linux-revisted/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/desktop-linux-revisted/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
Linux enthusiasts have some kind of weird obsession with Linux market share. Compound this with the fact that it&amp;rsquo;s almost impossible to determine accurately, with estimates ranging from lows of 0.5% to sky-high predictions like 5%. That&amp;rsquo;s a whole order of magnitude of estimates! Each end of the spectrum posits a completely different future of Linux, so let&amp;rsquo;s get started digging into this!
The first thing to remember is that 90% of the things written on the Internet were written by people who completely didn&amp;rsquo;t understand what they were saying.</description></item><item><title>DIY Cloud Gaming</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/diy-cloud-gaming/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/diy-cloud-gaming/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
Cloud gaming sucks. Here&amp;rsquo;s Wikipedia&amp;rsquo;s summary of its many flaws:
This approach provides several disadvantages, notably forcing the user to consistently maintain a high-speed internet connection to an external organization. This built-in barrier to entry not only locks out users who wish to play video games in areas without this internet connection, but also precludes the player from owning their personal copy of the software, and permanently locks the user into a rental agreement, tying the purchase of the game to the solvency of the streaming provider (if the company goes out of business, the game ceases to exist).</description></item><item><title>Self-hosting Sucks</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/self-hosting-sucks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/self-hosting-sucks/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
After one month of self-hosting, if there&amp;rsquo;s one thing I&amp;rsquo;ve learned, it&amp;rsquo;s that self-hosting sucks. As I&amp;rsquo;ve said in a previous post, self-hosting is not the solution to our privacy woes. So why exactly does it suck so much? Here&amp;rsquo;s a short timeline of the past month:
My Discord-Matrix bridge goes down over a weekend and I don&amp;rsquo;t find out for several days.</description></item><item><title>The Scary S Words</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/scary-s-words/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/scary-s-words/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
There are two S words that will plunge any Linux forum into endless debate: systemd and standardization. Just look at what happened on #archlinux:archlinux.org: a lengthly flamewar perpetrated by systemd haters which took through debates about standardization, market share, and gun culture (Yes, this did happen), leading to several bans of longtime regulars. So what makes these two words so divisive and controversial?
Let&amp;rsquo;s start with systemd.</description></item><item><title>Matrix: Less Degenerate than Discord?</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/matrix-less-degenerate-than-discord/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/matrix-less-degenerate-than-discord/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
Matrix is great. It&amp;rsquo;s secure. it&amp;rsquo;s decentralized. The perfect free and open source replacement for Discord, right?
Well, there&amp;rsquo;s a few problems with this vision of the future. The first? To put it simply, no one uses Matrix. OK, maybe 100000 people use it at most, but that&amp;rsquo;s nothing compared to the tens of millions of Discord users. The Arch Linux Matrix room recently hit a major milestone: 10000 people.</description></item><item><title>Fixing Bugs Isn't Hard!</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/fixing-bugs-isnt-hard/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/fixing-bugs-isnt-hard/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
A few days ago, I wanted to record my screen, and in process, I discovered this bug. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem like a very complicated bug, right? Just look through the code, find out what&amp;rsquo;s wrong, and send in a pull request! Or is it that easy?
The first issue is that Spectacle&amp;rsquo;s code is not exactly the most readable code out there, but I was able to identify [line 209 in GUI/KSMainWindow.</description></item><item><title>Why Self-hosting is not the Solution</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/self-hosting-is-not-the-solution/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/self-hosting-is-not-the-solution/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
So you hate tech giants. You hate Google for removing &amp;ldquo;don&amp;rsquo;t be evil&amp;rdquo; from their code of conduct. You hate Microsoft for making Office and not providing a Linux port, or even worse, creating the dreaded Microsoft Losedows. You hate Crapple&amp;rsquo;s walled garden. You hate Amazon. You hate Facebook and Twitter and all the other closed social media sites. But&amp;hellip;
These giants have truly permeated through all the aspects of our digital lives.</description></item><item><title>Self-hosting is Hard!</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/self-hosting-is-hard/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/self-hosting-is-hard/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
It&amp;rsquo;s been over a week since I&amp;rsquo;ve completed my build and switched over many things to self-hosting. Here&amp;rsquo;s how it went:
It works! Remote desktop VNC works perfectly. OK, fine, I haven&amp;rsquo;t figured out clipboad sharing yet, but other than that, it&amp;rsquo;s perfect. I also tried Xrdp but didn&amp;rsquo;t have much luck. There&amp;rsquo;s also X2Go which bundles some extra perks like sound and clipboard sharing, but the image quality is blurry at times.</description></item><item><title>Worst First Build - Homelab Operational!</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/worst-first-build-6/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/worst-first-build-6/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
Over the past week, I&amp;rsquo;ve been getting my new build set up. It&amp;rsquo;s been quite satisfying: I&amp;rsquo;ll run into more than my fair share of issues, but problem solving for the win!
The OS installation went relatively smoothly. Partitioning disks was a bit tricky but I got it to work. I wanted to try out systemd-networkd and systemd-boot for my new server, and I had to spend some time researching documentation.</description></item><item><title>Worst First Build - Live on PCPartPicker!</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/worst-first-build-5/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/worst-first-build-5/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
It&amp;rsquo;s time to go full circle! I first started planning my build using Logical Increments and PCPartPicker and I can&amp;rsquo;t appreciate how much they&amp;rsquo;ve helped me the confusing world of PC building. Now that my build is &amp;ldquo;finished&amp;rdquo;, or more accurately, functional, it&amp;rsquo;s time to publish it on PCPartPicker!
Here&amp;rsquo;s some anticlimactic images of the completed build:
Here&amp;rsquo;s the writeup that I did for the build:</description></item><item><title>Worst First Build - How to Get a Free GPU During the World's Worst GPU Shortage Ever</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/worst-first-build-4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/worst-first-build-4/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
The Great GPU Shortage continues to smash records. We live in ludicrous times indeed, where it&amp;rsquo;s considered lucky to win a lottery to buy a $330 GPU&amp;hellip; at a $200 markup! The barometer of Bitcoin and Ethereum prices continues to skyrocket, and my chances of finally getting a GPU and finishing my build were dimming every day with no end in sight.
But finish my build I did, with a GPU that ended up costing a grand total of&amp;hellip; $0.</description></item><item><title>Worst First Build - The Quest for a GPU</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/worst-first-build-3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/worst-first-build-3/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
Last Wednesday, March 10th, was going to be the day. The day I finally could complete a functioning (but incomplete) build. My slightly overpriced RAM sticks (RAM prices were creeping upward sinisterly so I decided I probably shouldn&amp;rsquo;t wait longer. Probably a bad move, too, but whatever.) were arriving, and it was going to be momentous. I was going to boot up an Arch USB drive, SSH in, and get the party going.</description></item><item><title>Worst First Build - The Sad Saga Continues</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/worst-first-build-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/worst-first-build-2/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
What a perfect time to build a PC: massive supply chain disruptions, cryptocurrencies driving up GPU prices through the roof, (scalper) bot wars, and a pesky little thing called the coronavirus murdering 2.5 million people (that last one probably sounds completely alien to anyone before 2019). Just perfect!
Anyways&amp;hellip; for over 40 days since buying an overpriced 5600X (because of insane taxes, that&amp;rsquo;s what), there were a grand total of zero deals.</description></item><item><title>The Web Sucks!</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/web-sucks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/web-sucks/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
suckless.org really hates the web. I&amp;rsquo;ll quote them directly:
It has enabled the global information exchange, mass surveillance, studies in social control, allowed revolutions, made a fortune for many billionaires and in the meanwhile ruined our climate: the web.
There is an industry which is specialized on extending the resource usage to display just some characters on your display. Millions of jobs are based on outputting HTML in an inefficient way.</description></item><item><title>How to Break a Rolling Release</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/break-rolling-release/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/break-rolling-release/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
It&amp;rsquo;s the day! Plasma 5.21 is out!
First, let me flex my neofetch to answer all your burning questions about my OS:
Now, time for the update. The big one. The closest thing to a point update in a rolling release. And&amp;hellip;
Lots of updates, but Plasma 5.21 is not one of them.
Digging a bit deeper, it looks like it&amp;rsquo;s still in testing. Looks like we need to enable it first.</description></item><item><title>I, BTW, use Arch</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/i-btw-use-arch/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/i-btw-use-arch/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
Ubuntu (you thought this was going to be about Arch, didn&amp;rsquo;t you?) is a great distro. Cue Reddit screaming. Look on any web forum and you&amp;rsquo;ll find people patronizing Ubuntu. Why? For having a straightforward installer that I can use to get Ubuntu up and running in half an hour with my favorite apps? For being the most supported distro by third-party developers? (They always have a PPA) For dominating server OSes in terms of market share?</description></item><item><title>Worst First Build</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/worst-first-build/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/worst-first-build/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
My laptop&amp;rsquo;s starting to get old. I mean, it works perfectly fine for the most part, but open up a few Google Docs at the same time and watch it struggle to load them: its age is starting to show. Or try to run Zoom (sandboxed in a browser, of course) and anything else at the simultaneously, and you&amp;rsquo;ll get an ugly surprise when your Zoom audio starts crackling up really bad and the other app lags like crazy.</description></item><item><title>How Windows Update Saved My Computer from... Windows Update</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/windows-update/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/windows-update/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
If I had to name the single thing that I most hate about Windows, it would probably be Windows update. I have a long and complicated history with Windows update. Throw in Windows Insider, and you have the perfect recipe for disaster!
A close encounter So my experience with Windows update begins about two or three years ago, when I noticed the cute ninja cat of Windows Insider lounging at the bottom of the Updates panel in the Windows 10 settings app.</description></item><item><title>The Worst Init System's Best Tool</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/worst-init-system-best-tool/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/worst-init-system-best-tool/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
True story: a few weeks ago, I wanted to test out SuperTuxKart but I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to install it on my computer. I had a few options: use a virtual machine and suffer terrible graphics performance, use Docker and suffer the pain of trying to set up graphical acceleration; or use LXC/LXD and suffer the (massive) pain of trying to set up basically anything. I ended up just installing SuperTuxKart to get out of the triple-sided dilemma.</description></item><item><title>Why WMs Suck</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/why-wms-suck/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/why-wms-suck/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
WM fans, don&amp;rsquo;t kill me for saying this, but window managers suck. To see why, let&amp;rsquo;s examine the process of installing and configuring a WM.
Installing a WM OK, I&amp;rsquo;ll admit that this step is much faster. Most WMs are only a few megabytes and take a few seconds to install, even with slow package managers like urpmi. Try installing something like KDE Plasma on Mageia or even Arch.</description></item><item><title>The Linux Office?</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/linux-office/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/linux-office/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
OK, LibreOffice may not be the most loved application out there, but it&amp;rsquo;s enough for most people. I use LibreOffice even on Windows! However, there is one thing about it that bothers me: the hideous icons! At first, I thought it might be caused be anti-aliasing or my screen scaling (currently set at 1.5x so everything&amp;rsquo;s not tiny) but nope! The icons stayed hideous no matter what I did.</description></item><item><title>iOS Jailbreaking || Why the World is Just a Programming Task</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/ios-jailbreaking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/ios-jailbreaking/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog
Let&amp;rsquo;s do this &amp;ldquo;episode&amp;rdquo; style:
Episode 0 (Because no true programmer would start a list with 1) In fourth or fifth grade, a friend told me about all the cool things he was doing with his jailbroken iPhone.
This is EXACTLY like your friend telling you about how fun and awesome competitive programming is.
I wasn&amp;rsquo;t impressed.
Episode 1 Five years later&amp;hellip;
After doing some TI-Nspire, Wii U, and Switch hacking, I set my eyes on my lowly iPhone 6s with a cracked screen that I&amp;rsquo;m procrastinating to fix.</description></item><item><title>Arch Memes</title><link>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/arch-memes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ta180m.github.io/posts/arch-memes/</guid><description>Originally posted on my old blog</description></item></channel></rss>